Michael Adam Berry

web developer

Contact

Address

648 Manhattan Ave Brookyn, NY 11222

Email

me@adamberrv.dev

Phone

270.314.7807

website

adamberry.dev

Profile

A passionate technologist with a broad skill set, I create bespoke experiences on the web. I have extensive experience with HTML, CSS, Javascript and modern frameworks and libraries, but I believe my true strength as a developer lies in my ability to solve complex problems, learn new technologies quickly, and collaborate with teammembers, clients and managers. I strive to be a champion for a thriving, accessible and inclulsive internet and an active member of the New York City developer community.

Experience

Open Source Web Developer

New York | 20017 - Present

- Developing open source web applications and data visualizations.
- · Contributing to projects like 5Calls and Gatsby.

Freelance Web Developer

New York City | 2019 - Present

- Creating websites for artists, writers, and small businesses
- Providing long term value by identifying the technologies for each clients specific needs.

Associate Project Manager

Seigfried's Basement Incorporated | New York | 2015-2019

Assisting in the planning, build, and installation of scenery for large scale live events throughout New York City. Clients included New York Fashion Week, Nike Pop Stores, The Veuve Clicquot Polo Classic.

Actor

Film and Theatre - SAG | AEA | New York | 2009-2019

- Actor in feature films and plays in New York City and regionally across the US. Noteable projects include A Birder's Guide To Everything (with Ben Kingsly), Private Romeo (LA Outfest Award for Best Ensemble)
- Founding Member of Exit Pursued By A Bear, a theatre company that remixes classic plays in a modern social environment.

Education

Bachelors of Fine Arts

Carnegie Mellon University 2005-2009

Certificate of Completion

Python for Data Science Coursera / University of Michigan

Certificate of Completion

CS50 / Intro to Computer Science EDX / Harvard University

Certificate of Completion

Advanced React
TylerMcguinnes.com

Skills

- HTML
- Node
- Three.js

- CSS
- Express
- SVG

- JavaScript
- D3
- Adobe Illustrator

- React
- Svelte
- Basic Python